万事通技术支持
他肯定能帮我们  快走吧
I bet he can help us. Come on!
欢迎回到搜索栏  女士
Welcome back to the search bar, madam.
我希望你找到了
I hope you were able to find
一个令你满意的早餐玉米煎饼
a satisfactory breakfast burrito...
我早上为您提供了这个搜索结果
based upon the search results I provided this morning.
现在万事通有什么能帮到您的
What can KnowsMore help you find now?
我要去哪里找芭蕾...
Where can I find ballet...?
芭蕾舞鞋  芭蕾舞课  芭蕾舞团
Ballet shoes? Ballet classes? Ballet folklorico?
...舞裤
...tights?
女童小号
Girls' size small.
小玛德琳现在开始学芭蕾了  是吗
Oh, little Madeline's trying ballet now, is she?
我希望能坚持得比足球课长
I hope this lasts longer than the soccer phase.
搜索
针对"芭蕾舞裤  女童小号"
I found 23 million results
我找到了2300万条结果
for ballet tights, girls' size small.